{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190665634","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190665633"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 9f328751-bacd-4978-b7a5-2d22c04ba4f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_haki_yeye-haki-mara"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190698026","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190698026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190699643","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190699643"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190708717","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190708717"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190715625","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190715625"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190723451","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190723451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190726032","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190726031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190735917","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190735916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190737405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190737404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190746512","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190746512"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190748729","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190748729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190757327","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190757326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190759199","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190759199"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190764620","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190764620"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190774167","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190774167"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190776289","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190776289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190784916","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190784915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190786325","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190786325"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190796785","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190796785"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190803485","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190803485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190805888","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190805888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190816148","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190816148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190818469","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190818469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190825093","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190825093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190831345","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190831345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190845430","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190845430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190853055","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190853054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190856384","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190856384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190867622","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190867619"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190873185","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190873185"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" ab841376-a502-4b2c-a837-ec1240bd9124"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190887925","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190887925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 635c19a0-bd24-4e5e-9c43-b8e73351463a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kasi_nane-ziwa-kasi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kasi"," userResponse":" kasi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190896766","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190896766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 635c19a0-bd24-4e5e-9c43-b8e73351463a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kavu_haha-zamu-kavu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kavu"," userResponse":" kavu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190906065","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190906064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 635c19a0-bd24-4e5e-9c43-b8e73351463a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kapu_simu-kapu-kisa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kapu"," userResponse":" kapu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190914800","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190914800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 635c19a0-bd24-4e5e-9c43-b8e73351463a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kati_yaya-ebei-kati"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kati"," userResponse":" kati"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190923407","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190923407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 635c19a0-bd24-4e5e-9c43-b8e73351463a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kama_tele-zipu-kama"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kama"," userResponse":" kama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190931569","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190931569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 635c19a0-bd24-4e5e-9c43-b8e73351463a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kapu_kapu-mmea-hema"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kapu"," userResponse":" kapu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190940844","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190940844"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 635c19a0-bd24-4e5e-9c43-b8e73351463a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kali_kali-lulu-kiio"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kali"," userResponse":" kali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190950840","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190950840"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 635c19a0-bd24-4e5e-9c43-b8e73351463a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kama_ndio-elsa-kama"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kama"," userResponse":" kama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190960469","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190960469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 635c19a0-bd24-4e5e-9c43-b8e73351463a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kale_kiti-wiki-kale"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kale"," userResponse":" kale"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190968539","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190968538"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 635c19a0-bd24-4e5e-9c43-b8e73351463a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kama_kama-mzee-nane"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kama"," userResponse":" kama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190974294","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190974291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 635c19a0-bd24-4e5e-9c43-b8e73351463a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kama_kama-mzee-nane"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549190980902","data":{"timestamp":" 1549190980901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" caf2b1ac-2ccb-4c4c-a39c-bee146a59f8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191000823","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191000822"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" caf2b1ac-2ccb-4c4c-a39c-bee146a59f8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191003668","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191003668"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" caf2b1ac-2ccb-4c4c-a39c-bee146a59f8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191003771","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191003771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" caf2b1ac-2ccb-4c4c-a39c-bee146a59f8f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191016206","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191016205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191016728","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191016727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191017327","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191017326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191018184","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191018184"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191028199","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191028198"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191029899","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191029899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191031304","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191031304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191033320","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191033320"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191035300","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191035299"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba ana meno makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191037704","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191037703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191038205","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191038205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191038751","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191038750"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191039583","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191039583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191040151","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191040150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191040530","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191040530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191042608","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191042608"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191043307","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191043307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191043714","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191043713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191044937","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191044936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191046407","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191046407"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191048110","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191048110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191048278","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191048277"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191048988","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191048987"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba ana meno makali vile vile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILE"," userResponse":" VILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191051183","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191051182"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPA"," userResponse":" PAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191051681","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191051681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191052164","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191052163"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191052807","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191052806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191053710","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191053710"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191055679","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191055679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PAPA"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191056458","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191056458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPA"," userResponse":" PAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191057488","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191057487"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191057490","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191057490"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191058791","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191058791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191059839","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191059839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" START_MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191061571","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191061568"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191062543","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191062543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191064379","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191064379"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa ana meno makali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191066139","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191066137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191066717","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191066717"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191067416","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191067416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191067601","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191067600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191068346","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191068346"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191068765","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191068765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191069311","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191069308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191070527","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191070527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191072232","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191072231"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191072408","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191072408"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191073941","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191073940"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191076749","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191076748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191078402","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191078402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191079357","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191079357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191081674","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191081674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191082790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191082789"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191086175","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191086174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191088346","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191088345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191088356","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191088355"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191090425","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191090425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini baadhi ya wanyama wana meno makali?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191092873","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191092873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191092894","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191092894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191093406","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191093406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191094074","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191094073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191094366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191094366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191095112","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191095112"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191095467","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191095466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191096290","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191096289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" AJILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191096353","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191096353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191097221","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191097220"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAGA"," userResponse":" KUSAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191098926","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191098925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191100170","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191100170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191101107","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191101106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191101495","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191101495"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191101900","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191101899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191103377","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191103377"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191104722","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191104721"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191105681","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191105681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191106597","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191106597"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191107496","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191107496"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191108782","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191108782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191108965","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191108965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" AJILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191109200","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191109200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191110002","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191110001"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAGA"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191112100","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191112100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe ana meno ya nguvu kwa ajili ya kusaga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191114454","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191114452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191114998","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191114997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191115703","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191115703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191119487","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191119487"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191120399","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191120399"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191120795","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191120795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege hana meno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191122442","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191122442"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191123483","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191123483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191123991","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191123991"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" HULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191124622","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191124622"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMNA"," userResponse":" NAMNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191125618","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191125617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191127541","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191127540"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" HULA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191128543","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191128542"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191129755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191129754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191129921","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191129921"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191130921","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191130921"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191132245","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191132245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" HULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191133168","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191133168"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAMNA"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191134235","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191134234"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NAMNA"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191135804","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191135804"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMNA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191136955","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191136955"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" START_NDEGE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191139963","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191139963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndege hula namna gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191142238","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191142238"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191142727","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191142727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191143329","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191143328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191143561","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191143561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191144197","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191144197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191145226","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191145225"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191147375","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191147375"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191147696","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191147696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191148784","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191148784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191149166","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191149165"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191150360","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191150360"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191150818","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191150818"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUBWA"," userResponse":" MAKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191153605","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191153605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191153920","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191153920"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191154463","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191154463"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191154684","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191154684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191155383","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191155382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191157178","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191157178"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191158191","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191158191"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191159722","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191159721"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191160217","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191160216"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191161135","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191161134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191161307","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191161307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191161875","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191161875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191162836","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191162835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191164227","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191164226"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa na meno ya mbele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191166486","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191166486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191167114","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191167114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191167239","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191167239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191167550","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191167549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191169035","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191169035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALING"," userResponse":" YALING"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191169058","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191169057"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OKA"," userResponse":" OKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191171841","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191171841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191173322","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191173322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191173331","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191173330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191173339","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191173339"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191174618","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191174618"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALING"," userResponse":" YALING"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191174723","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191174723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Meno yangu ya mbele yaling'oka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OKA"," userResponse":" OKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191176389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191176388"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191177261","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191177261"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191177822","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191177822"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191179287","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191179287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANGAPI"," userResponse":" MANGAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191180722","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191180722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191181402","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191181402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191181913","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191181913"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191183337","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191183337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" MANGAPI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191184876","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191184876"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191185654","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191185653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191187992","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191187992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191188473","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191188473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANGAPI"," userResponse":" MANGAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191190484","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191190482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191190593","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191190593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANGAPI"," userResponse":" MANGAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191196510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191196509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 3fff120e-db14-4bdd-b851-7550b250c6a9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ka.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191219031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191219030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 75a6ab07-316e-4a9c-8473-6150744d058a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ka.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" kati_kati_kalio_kayanja"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ka.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191225666","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191225666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 75a6ab07-316e-4a9c-8473-6150744d058a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ka.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_karo_kakake_kabla"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ka.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191232286","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191232285"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 75a6ab07-316e-4a9c-8473-6150744d058a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ka.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" kata_kata_katikati_kazi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ka.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191238906","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191238906"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 75a6ab07-316e-4a9c-8473-6150744d058a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ka.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" karibuni_karatasi_karibuni_kasa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ka.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191245539","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191245537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 75a6ab07-316e-4a9c-8473-6150744d058a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ka.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" kaka_kaka_kana_kanyada"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ka.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191252135","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191252135"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 75a6ab07-316e-4a9c-8473-6150744d058a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ka.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" karibu_katikati_karibu_kabla"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ka.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191258762","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191258762"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 75a6ab07-316e-4a9c-8473-6150744d058a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ka.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" kali_kali_kayanja_kakake"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ka.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191265416","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191265416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 75a6ab07-316e-4a9c-8473-6150744d058a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ka.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" kanyada_kasa_karo_kanyada"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ka.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191272026","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191272026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 75a6ab07-316e-4a9c-8473-6150744d058a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ka.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" karibuni_kambo_karibuni_kapu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ka.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191278659","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191278659"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 75a6ab07-316e-4a9c-8473-6150744d058a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ka.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" kati_kawaida_kando_kati"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ka.show.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191291731","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191291731"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 75a6ab07-316e-4a9c-8473-6150744d058a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ka.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" kati_kawaida_kando_kati"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191300814","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191300814"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 75a6ab07-316e-4a9c-8473-6150744d058a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ka.show.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kati_kawaida_kando_kati"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191311256","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191311256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191314276","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191314276"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191315834","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191315834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kapu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAPU"," userResponse":" KAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191319162","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191319162"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kapu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAPU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191320729","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191320729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATI"," userResponse":" KATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191323948","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191323948"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191325505","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191325505"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALI"," userResponse":" KALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191329052","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191329052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191330605","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191330605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191334375","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191334375"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191335923","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191335923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191339236","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191339236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191340803","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191340803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191344185","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191344185"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191345732","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191345732"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANA"," userResponse":" KANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191348893","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191348892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191350450","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191350450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASI"," userResponse":" KASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191353873","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191353872"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191355436","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191355436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATA"," userResponse":" KATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191358949","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191358949"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ka.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191360962","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191360962"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" kata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191361122","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191361122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191365986","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191365985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ka.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191372978","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191372978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 21aa6b50-b821-458b-b327-641d505176b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ka.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191379710","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191379710"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" a5c43153-1963-4fff-8265-ccdd312e97b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191399862","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191399862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" a5c43153-1963-4fff-8265-ccdd312e97b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191402613","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191402611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" a5c43153-1963-4fff-8265-ccdd312e97b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191402724","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191402723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" a5c43153-1963-4fff-8265-ccdd312e97b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ki.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191408748","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191408748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" a5c43153-1963-4fff-8265-ccdd312e97b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191413875","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191413874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" a5c43153-1963-4fff-8265-ccdd312e97b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191425339","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191425338"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" d9386b4c-1662-438a-91b3-bab4fd3f1072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191425861","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191425861"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" d9386b4c-1662-438a-91b3-bab4fd3f1072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191426405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191426405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" d9386b4c-1662-438a-91b3-bab4fd3f1072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBINGU"," userResponse":" MBINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191426647","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191426647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" d9386b4c-1662-438a-91b3-bab4fd3f1072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191426859","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191426859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" d9386b4c-1662-438a-91b3-bab4fd3f1072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191427521","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191427521"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" d9386b4c-1662-438a-91b3-bab4fd3f1072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191427597","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191427596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" d9386b4c-1662-438a-91b3-bab4fd3f1072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191429019","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191429019"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" d9386b4c-1662-438a-91b3-bab4fd3f1072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191431931","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191431931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" d9386b4c-1662-438a-91b3-bab4fd3f1072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191432058","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191432058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" d9386b4c-1662-438a-91b3-bab4fd3f1072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191436929","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191436929"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" d9386b4c-1662-438a-91b3-bab4fd3f1072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ki.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191443935","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191443934"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" d9386b4c-1662-438a-91b3-bab4fd3f1072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191448861","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191448860"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" d9386b4c-1662-438a-91b3-bab4fd3f1072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191456298","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191456297"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" d9386b4c-1662-438a-91b3-bab4fd3f1072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191462814","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191462814"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 4e47ba99-0a28-4bd6-aa6a-423794a29558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191464044","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191464042"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 4e47ba99-0a28-4bd6-aa6a-423794a29558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191464119","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191464119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 4e47ba99-0a28-4bd6-aa6a-423794a29558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ki.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191469899","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191469898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 4e47ba99-0a28-4bd6-aa6a-423794a29558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191474176","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191474175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 4e47ba99-0a28-4bd6-aa6a-423794a29558"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191488275","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191488275"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" bbd7b4fb-ef07-46e6-bb19-4bac38fa12d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kima_bibi-kima-hawa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kima"," userResponse":" kima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191497300","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191497300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" bbd7b4fb-ef07-46e6-bb19-4bac38fa12d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kila_kila-rudi-kule"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kila"," userResponse":" kila"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191506762","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191506762"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" bbd7b4fb-ef07-46e6-bb19-4bac38fa12d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kisu_sura-nawe-kisu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kisu"," userResponse":" kisu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191515960","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191515960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" bbd7b4fb-ef07-46e6-bb19-4bac38fa12d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kila_hata-pana-kila"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kila"," userResponse":" hata"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191525901","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191525901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" bbd7b4fb-ef07-46e6-bb19-4bac38fa12d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kila_hata-pana-kila"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kila"," userResponse":" kila"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191536745","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191536744"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" bbd7b4fb-ef07-46e6-bb19-4bac38fa12d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kinu_kwao-kinu-sifa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kinu"," userResponse":" sifa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191546685","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191546685"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" bbd7b4fb-ef07-46e6-bb19-4bac38fa12d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kinu_kwao-kinu-sifa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kinu"," userResponse":" kinu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191556280","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191556279"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" bbd7b4fb-ef07-46e6-bb19-4bac38fa12d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kiio_bila-babu-kiio"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kiio"," userResponse":" kiio"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191566344","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191566344"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" bbd7b4fb-ef07-46e6-bb19-4bac38fa12d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kifo_kuku-goti-kifo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kifo"," userResponse":" kifo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191576725","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191576725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" bbd7b4fb-ef07-46e6-bb19-4bac38fa12d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kike_kana-kike-kuoa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kike"," userResponse":" kike"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191585600","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191585599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" bbd7b4fb-ef07-46e6-bb19-4bac38fa12d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kina_kina-nchi-yawe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kina"," userResponse":" kina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191595389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191595389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" bbd7b4fb-ef07-46e6-bb19-4bac38fa12d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kitu_kitu-baba-sisi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kitu"," userResponse":" kitu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191601126","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191601125"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" bbd7b4fb-ef07-46e6-bb19-4bac38fa12d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kitu_kitu-baba-sisi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191608790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191608789"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" bbd7b4fb-ef07-46e6-bb19-4bac38fa12d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ki.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kitu_kitu-baba-sisi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191641111","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191641111"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191643768","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191643768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191654895","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191654895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191658366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191658366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191664372","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191664371"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191675027","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191675027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191678069","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191678068"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191692073","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191692073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191702544","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191702544"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191716024","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191716024"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191727469","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191727469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191735384","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191735383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191739908","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191739908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191753317","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191753317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191759656","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191759656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191767003","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191767003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191769120","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191769120"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191780205","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191780205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191782654","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191782654"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191803979","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191803979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191810703","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191810703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191817678","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191817678"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191819171","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191819170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191830436","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191830436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191836299","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191836299"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" q"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191842425","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191842425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191867786","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191867786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191869107","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191869107"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191879055","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191879055"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191881160","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191881160"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191888131","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191888131"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ki.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191898945","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191898945"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191905879","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191905878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 205fdd7f-8b4b-4136-b5c3-fc045efb4054"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ki.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_ki__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191922395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191922395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kisu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191923481","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191923481"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kisu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISU"," userResponse":" KISU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191926562","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191926562"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191927600","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191927600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKI"," userResponse":" KIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191931084","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191931084"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191932121","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191932121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kina"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" KINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191934947","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191934947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kila"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191935154","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191935153"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kila"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191936154","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191936153"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kile"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILE"," userResponse":" KILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191938491","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191938491"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kile"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILE"," userResponse":" KILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191942206","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191942205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kipi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191943298","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191943298"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kipi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPI"," userResponse":" KIPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191946109","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191946109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191947149","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191947148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISA"," userResponse":" KISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191951027","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191951027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191952077","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191952077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIWE"," userResponse":" KIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191955409","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191955409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kifo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191956444","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191956444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kifo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFO"," userResponse":" KIFO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ki.rand.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191959867","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191959867"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" kifo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549191960026","data":{"timestamp":" 1549191960026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190203_134418"," gameId":" 6370e4a5-e553-407b-bf73-77c6fbaea906"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ki.rand.37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kifo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFO"," userResponse":" KIFO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}